<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Official Numix Blog</title>
    <description>The official blog of &#39;&#39;Numix Project&#39;&#39; - an open source project that is all about creating quality designed software product and artwork.Here we will post important announcements and blog about anything we feel is worthy writing about.
</description>
    <link>http://blog.numixproject.org//</link>
    <atom:link href="http://blog.numixproject.org//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2015 19:21:22 +0100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2015 19:21:22 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Every story has a beginning</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Greetings!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re reading this, it means that we’re already dead and you’ve 3 days to save the world from Dalek invasion. Help the world, Numix users, you’re its only hope! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ok, we are kidding, although you never know when those plungery bastards will invade us. :-)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Now, lets be serious for a difference.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, this is our &lt;strong&gt;official Numix blog&lt;/strong&gt; and in it we will post &lt;strong&gt;important announcements&lt;/strong&gt;, interesting &lt;strong&gt;stories&lt;/strong&gt; about numix, karaoke versions of us singing “Let it go” and anything else we think is blog posts material. It goes without saying that you should keep and eye on the blog and interfact with us in it.
We hope you will have enjoyable time and our blog and find it useful, informative and even slightly funny.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This concludes our first post, see you all in the comments here and on various social networks and of course in the next post.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2014 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.numixproject.org//numix/blog/2014/11/30/introducing-numix-blog.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.numixproject.org//numix/blog/2014/11/30/introducing-numix-blog.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>numix</category>
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
